<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<countries>
    <country>
        <name>Israel</name>
        <flag>israel</flag>
        <anthem>israel</anthem>
        <short>population: 7 millions</short>
        <details>
            Israel
            Country in Asia
            Israel or, officially the State of Israel, is a country in Western Asia, situated at the southeastern shore of the Mediterranean Sea.
            Capital: Jerusalem
            Prime minister: Benjamin Netanyahu
            Currency: Israeli new shekel
            President: Reuven Rivlin
            Official languages: Hebrew, Arabic
        </details>
    </country>
    <country>
        <name>France</name>
        <flag>france</flag>
        <anthem>france</anthem>
        <short>population: 66 millions</short>
        <details>
            France
            Country in Europe
            France, officially the French Republic, is a unitary sovereign state comprising territory in western Europe and several overseas regions and territories.
            Capital: Paris
            Dialing code: +33
            President: Franֳ§ois Hollande
            Prime minister: Manuel Valls
            Population: 66.03 million (2013)
        </details>
    </country>
    <country>
        <name>Norway</name>
        <flag>norway</flag>
        <anthem>norway</anthem>
        <short>population: 5 millions</short>
        <details>
            Norway
            Country in Europe
            Norway, officially the Kingdom of Norway, is a sovereign and unitary monarchy whose territory comprises the western portion of the Scandinavian Peninsula plus Jan Mayen and the Arctic archipelago of Svalbard. Wikipedia
            Capital: Oslo
            Currency: Norwegian krone
            Population: 5.084 million (2013) World Bank
            Official languages: Norwegian, Nynorsk, Bokmֳ¥l
            Colleges and Universities: University of Oslo, more
        </details>
    </country>
    <country>
        <name>Greece</name>
        <flag>greece</flag>
        <anthem>greece</anthem>
        <short>population: 11 millions</short>
        <details>
            Greece
            Country in Europe
            Greece, officially the Hellenic Republic and known since ancient times as Hellas, is a country located in southeastern Europe. According to the 2011 census, Greece's population is around 11 million.
            Capital: Athens
            Currency: Euro
            Prime minister: Alexis Tsipras
            Population: 11.03 million (2013) World Bank
            Official language: Greek
        </details>
    </country>
    <country>
        <name>United States</name>
        <flag>united_states</flag>
        <anthem>united_states</anthem>
        <short>population: 319 millions</short>
        <details>
            United States of America
            Country
            The United States of America, commonly referred to as the United States or America, is a federal republic consisting of 50 states and a federal district.
            Capital: Washington, D.C.
            Dialing code: +1
            ISO code: USA
            Population: 318.9 million (2014)
            President: Barack Obama
        </details>
    </country>
    <country>
        <name>Germany</name>
        <flag>germany</flag>
        <anthem>germany</anthem>
        <short>population: 80 millions</short>
        <details>
            Germany
            Country in Europe
            Germany, officially the Federal Republic of Germany, is a federal parliamentary republic in western-central Europe.
            Capital: Berlin
            Dialing code: +49
            Currency: Euro
            Population: 80.62 million (2013) World Bank
            Chancellor: Angela Merkel
        </details>
    </country>
    <country>
        <name>Jordan</name>
        <flag>jordan</flag>
        <anthem>jordan</anthem>
        <short>population: 6 millions</short>
        <details>
            Jordan
            Country in Asia
            Jordan, officially the Hashemite Kingdom of Jordan, is an Arab kingdom in the Middle East, on the East Bank of the Jordan River.
            Capital: Amman
            King: Abdullah II of Jordan
            Prime minister: Abdullah Ensour
            Continent: Asia
            Population: 6.459 million (2013) World Bank
            Official language: Arabic
        </details>
    </country>
    <country>
        <name>Brazil</name>
        <flag>brazil</flag>
        <anthem>brazil</anthem>
        <short>population: 202 millions</short>
        <details>
            Brazil
            Country in South America
            Brazil, officially the Federative Republic of Brazil, is the largest country in both South America and the Latin American region. It is the world's fifth largest country, both by geographical area and by population.
            Capital: Brasֳ­lia
            Dialing code: +55
            Currency: Brazilian real
            President: Dilma Rousseff
            Official language: Portuguese
        </details>
    </country>
    <country>
        <name>New Zealand</name>
        <flag>new_zealand</flag>
        <anthem>new_zealand</anthem>
        <short>population: 4 millions</short>
        <details>
            New Zealand
            Country in Oceania
            New Zealand is an island country in the southwestern Pacific Ocean. The country geographically comprises two main landmasses ג€“ that of the North Island, or Te Ika-a-Mִui, and the South Island, or Te Waipounamu ג€“ and numerous smaller islands.
            Capital: Wellington
            Dialing code: +64
            Currency: New Zealand dollar
            Population: 4.471 million (2013) World Bank
            Continent: Oceania
        </details>
    </country>
    <country>
        <name>China</name>
        <flag>china</flag>
        <anthem>china</anthem>
        <short>population: 1,357 millions</short>
        <details>
            China
            Country in Asia
            China, officially the People's Republic of China, is a sovereign state located in East Asia. It is the world's most populous country, with a population of over 1.35 billion. Wikipedia
            Capital: Beijing
            Population: 1.357 billion (2013) World Bank
            Currency: Renminbi
            Gross domestic product: 9.24 trillion USD (2013) World Bank
            President: Xi Jinping
            GDP per capita: 6,807.43 USD (2013) World Bank
        </details>
    </country>
    <country>
        <name>Thailand</name>
        <flag>thailand</flag>
        <anthem>thailand</anthem>
        <short>population: 67 millions</short>
        <details>
            Thailand
            Country in Asia
            Thailand, officially the Kingdom of Thailand, formerly known as Siam, is a country at the centre of the Indochina peninsula in Southeast Asia.
            Capital: Bangkok
            Dialing code: +66
            ISO code: THA
            Currency: Thai baht
            Official language: Thai
        </details>
    </country>
    <country>
        <name>Switzerland</name>
        <flag>switzerland</flag>
        <anthem>switzerland</anthem>
        <short>population: 8 millions</short>
        <details>
            Switzerland
            Country in Europe
            Switzerland, officially the Swiss Confederation, is a federal parliamentary republic consisting of 26 cantons, with Bern as the seat of the federal authorities, the so-called Bundesstadt.
            Dialing code: +41
            ISO code: CHE
            Currency: Swiss franc
            Official languages: French, German, Romansh, Italian
            Colleges and Universities: ETH Zurich, University of Zurich, more
        </details>
    </country>
    <country>
        <name>Australia</name>
        <flag>australia</flag>
        <anthem>australia</anthem>
        <short>population: 23 millions</short>
        <details>
            Australia
            Country
            Australia, officially the Commonwealth of Australia, is an Oceanian country comprising the mainland of the Australian continent, the island of Tasmania, and numerous smaller islands. It is the world's sixth-largest country by total area.
            Capital: Canberra
            Dialing code: +61
            Currency: Australian dollar
            Governor-general: Peter Cosgrove
            Prime minister: Tony Abbott
        </details>
    </country>
    <country>
        <name>Romania</name>
        <flag>romania</flag>
        <anthem>romania</anthem>
        <short>population: 20.3 millions</short>
        <details>
            Romania
            Country in Europe
            Romania is a central European country known for the forested region of Transylvania, preserved medieval towns such as Sighiֵoara and many fortified churches and castles, notably clifftop Bran Castle, long associated with the Dracula legend. The area is ringed by the Carpathian Mountains, which are popular for trekking, climbing, skiing and bathing in natural thermal spas.
            Capital: Bucharest
            Dialing code: +40
            Currency: Romanian leu
            Continent: Europe
            Official language: Romanian
        </details>
    </country>
    <country>
        <name>Mexico</name>
        <flag>mexico</flag>
        <anthem>mexico</anthem>
        <short>population: 119 millions</short>
        <details>
            Mexico
            Country in North America
            Mexico is a country between the U.S. and Central America beaches on its Pacific and Gulf of Mexico coastlines and a diverse landscape of mountains, deserts and jungles. Ancient ruins such as Teotihuacan (Aztec) and Chichen Itza (Mayan) are scattered throughout the country, as are Spanish colonial-era towns. In capital Mexico City, upscale shops, renowned museums and gourmet restaurants cater to modern life.
            Capital: Mexico City
            Dialing code: +52
            Founded: September 27, 1821
            Currency: Mexican peso
            President: Enrique Peֳ±a Nieto
        </details>
    </country>
</countries>